<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>K.D. Murray</title>
    <link>https://kdmurray.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on K.D. Murray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 19:18:34 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kdmurray.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Play - The Drive to Make a Thing</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/12/the-drive-to-make-a-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 19:18:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/12/the-drive-to-make-a-thing/</guid>
      
        <description>Yet another Internet nerd jumping on the Minecraft Letsplay bandwagon?
Yes. In a way&amp;hellip;
Somewhere, not too deep down I hope, is a content creator who used to actually take pride and find joy in creating content. That seems to have fallen away almost entirely over the last several years. And&amp;hellip; I feel the need to justify some of my playing time.
I love the work I do with other people, particularly my production work for Knightwise, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like nearly enough.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iced Coffee Engineering</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/06/iced-coffee-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/06/iced-coffee-engineering/</guid>
      
        <description>Over the past week or so it&amp;rsquo;s been pretty warm here on the Canadian West Coast. That&amp;rsquo;s led me to want to drink a lot more iced coffee than usual. The downside of this being, of course, that take-out coffee is way more expensive than at-home coffee. So it was time to find a home-grown solution to this problem.
I&amp;rsquo;ve started to make the majority of my home-based coffee in a french press and that&amp;rsquo;s done a fine job for me of getting my morning coffee with a minimum amount of hassle and an end product that I really enjoy, thanks in part to James Hoffman&amp;rsquo;s Ultimate French Press technique.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thai Red Curry With Prawns</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/thai-red-curry-with-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 15:18:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/thai-red-curry-with-prawns/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  200-250 grams frozen raw prawns 1 small onion 2 carrots 1 broccoli crown 1 bell pepper 2 cloves garlic 1 tbsp fresh grated ginger 2 tbsp red curry paste 1 can coconut milk (full-fat) 1 tbsp brown sugar (or demerera, or coconut sugar) 1 tbsp soy sauce optional 1-2 jalepeño or other chiles to taste  Method  Thaw prawns in cool water while you prep the vegetables Break down all the veggies into pieces that will cook in a similar amount of time  peppers will cook the quickest looking for ~2 cups of veggies   Heat coconut milk and curry paste over medium heat, stirring occasionally until paste is fully incorporated and bubbles begin to appear Add soy sauce, sugar, garlic, ginger and onions to the coconut milk, simmer for 2 minutes Add prawns and simmer for 5 minutes - add 2 minutes if not thawed Add veggies in stages by hardness every 3-4 minutes Once all ingredients are added, cook until desired doneness of veggies is reached, probably 3-4 minutes This recipe goes really well with Baked Brown Rice  </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Brown Rice</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/baked-brown-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/baked-brown-rice/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  1 cups long grain brown rice 2 cups water 1 tbsp butter or olive oil 1/2 tsp salt  Method  Preheat oven to 400°F (200°C) Boil watter Combine all ingredients in a covered casserole Cover and bake for 1 hour  If your oven heats unevenly you may need to rotate the casserole</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Analog Tools</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/06/using-analog-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 15:46:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/06/using-analog-tools/</guid>
      
        <description>For the last four years I&amp;rsquo;ve been a fountain pen user, some might even say an enthusiast. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using very old technology to help me navigate my otherwise very modern and digital world. Why? Because it makes me think&amp;hellip; and it&amp;rsquo;s fun.
I never grew up with fountain pens. I understand that there are places in the world today that still tech kids to write with them, and that in many cases those students can&amp;rsquo;t wait to get away from these messy devices and start using something more modern like a ballpoint pen.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Zucchini Muffins</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/banana-zucchini-muffins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 17:54:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/banana-zucchini-muffins/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  2 1/2 cups all purpose flour 1 1/2 tsp baking soda 1 1/2 tsp baking powder 1 tsp salt 4 bananas, mashed 1 cup zucchini, grated 1/3 cup brown sugar 1 egg, beaten 1/2 cup butter, melted * 1 tsp vanilla optional 1/3 cup shredded unsweetened coconut optional 1/3 cup chopped walnuts  Method  Pre-heat oven to 350 degrees F (180 degrees C) Combine sugar, bananas, zucchini, butter, egg and vanilla in a mixing bowl Mix remaining ingredients in a large bowl Pour wet over dry and mix just until combined DO NOT OVERMIX YOUR MUFFINS Portion into muffin tins and bake for 20-25 minutes  For mini-muffin tins, bake 15-20 mins    </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WSL Manual Install</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/07/wsl-manual-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/07/wsl-manual-install/</guid>
      
        <description>If you happen to be in a situation where you would like to take advantage of Microsoft Windows subsystem for Linux but don&amp;rsquo;t have access to the Microsoft store, there is hope. The one largest caveat is that you need to have permission to install the windows subsystem for, without that the rest of this advice is useless, but once you have done that and rebooted your machine you&amp;rsquo;re ready to move on to the next phase which is find yourself some Linux.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year of Self</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/01/year-of-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/01/year-of-self/</guid>
      
        <description>For the past couple of years I&amp;rsquo;ve eschewed the practice of the New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolution in favour of broader goals or themes for the year. These have been helpful for me in providing an overall direction or guidepost for me as I work to make incremental improvements or changes throughout the year.
Where I&amp;rsquo;ve been&amp;hellip; The first of these, &amp;ldquo;Year of Less&amp;rdquo;, helped me to de-clutter mentally and physically, as well as direct my efforts towards a few specific projects and tasks.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Resolutions</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/agile-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/agile-resolutions/</guid>
      
        <description>We&amp;rsquo;re coming up to the end of the year again. I&amp;rsquo;m already starting to see the conversations starting about one of my most hated holiday season traditions: New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolutions.
Why am I such a grinch about self improvement? Why be opposed to people making a change for the better? I&amp;rsquo;m not, and I&amp;rsquo;m not. It&amp;rsquo;s not the change, or even the resolution itself that I have problems with, it&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;New Year&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; bit, and all of the associated issues that come with it.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Isn&#39;t Easy</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/simple-isnt-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/simple-isnt-easy/</guid>
      
        <description>Simple and easy &amp;ndash; These are two words that the English language allows people to confuse and that often become the source of misunderstandings of all sorts of sayings, advice, instructions and all manner of other communication.
What&amp;rsquo;s the difference? Easy is a measure of difficulty. If something is easy to do, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t require a great deal of effort and most people will be able to complete the task. The level of ease may depend on other factors, tall people can reach things more easily than short people for example, but generally speaking if something is easy the majority of people will be able to do it without much stress or difficulty.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharpen the Saw or Something</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/07/sharpen-the-saw-or-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/07/sharpen-the-saw-or-something/</guid>
      
        <description>Writing software is something I&amp;rsquo;ve loved to do for a very long time. But a little over a decade ago I made some career choices that meant my day-to-day no longer involved the production of code. I became an amateur developer. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve noodled around with things here and there, and have even managed to write some code that I or a small number of other people have used, but I find it hard to prioritize the time to do these things.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove the Barriers</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/06/remove-the-barriers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/06/remove-the-barriers/</guid>
      
        <description>The key to success is quite often getting started. The laws of conservation of energy apply to the macro scale of our lives as much as they do to the basic physical principles of the universe. A body at rest will remain at rest, while a body in motion will remain in motion.
For anyone who&amp;rsquo;s ever tried to &amp;ldquo;get in shape&amp;rdquo; the starting of that routine is often done with sheer willpower.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Case for an Open Podcast Directory</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/06/a-case-for-an-open-podcast-directory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/06/a-case-for-an-open-podcast-directory/</guid>
      
        <description>Podcasts have come a long way since people started just recording audio files and posting them to a website. Over the last decade the advent of RSS and mobile technology has provided publishers with the ability to produce text, audio and video content and have that content delivered directly to millions of subscribers around the world.
While many podcast enthusiasts find shows based on recommendations from friends or social media, the most common way to find new podcasts is through a podcast directory, specifically the iTunes podcast directory.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analogue Journey Update</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/06/analogue-journey-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/06/analogue-journey-update/</guid>
      
        <description>It has been about a year since I started my analog journey. It&amp;rsquo;s has had some ups and some downs, but overall the experience has been extremely positive. I stopped bouncing back and forth between task-tracking tools and productivity systems. I tore it all down, I went back to basics, and found simplest way of doing the things that needed to be done. Most importantly I found something that I could sustain over the long haul.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown Sugar Spice Rub</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/brown-sugar-spice-rub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/brown-sugar-spice-rub/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  4 parts brown sugar 2 parts kosher salt 1 part chili powder 1 part spices  cumin paprika garlic powder onion powder black pepper    Method  Mix all ingredients in a jar Add a lid and keep tightly sealed between uses Sprinkle liberally on chicken, pork or whatever else needs to be kicked up a notch  Note: Rub can also be made without sugar for applications where other sources of sweetness exist: i.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split Pea Soup</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/split-pea-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/split-pea-soup/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  2 Tbsp unsalted butter 1 cup chopped onion 1 Tbsp minced garlic 1 pinch kosher salt 12 oz (350g) green or yellow split peas 5 cups chicken broth 1Tbsp curry powder 1/2 cup diced ham (optional)  Method  Sweat the onions in the butter and salt for 2–3 mins until translucent Add the garlic to the sweat for 1–2 mins Add curry powder, peas and chicken broth Bring to a boil Cover and reduce to a simmer Simmer until peas are tender and not holding their shape (approx 40 minutes) Adjust seasoning to taste Puree with a stick blender (carefully, it&amp;rsquo;s hot!</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year of Done</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/01/year-of-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/01/year-of-done/</guid>
      
        <description>Done. It&amp;rsquo;s a word that conjures up finality. Following in the footsteps of 2017&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Year of Less&amp;rdquo; I have christened 2018 my &amp;ldquo;Year of Done&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m not a big fan of resolutions, be they New Year&amp;rsquo;s or otherwise. I do however like the idea of a theme for the year. After some soul-searching, add some cognitive down-time in the month of December, I have decided that &amp;ldquo;done&amp;rdquo; will be my theme for 2018.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clasic Pumpkin Pie</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/clasic-pumpkin-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/clasic-pumpkin-pie/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients Crust  2 9&amp;quot; frozen pie shells Yes, making your own would be more &amp;ldquo;classic.&amp;rdquo; I never do.  Filling  4 eggs 28oz pumpkin puree 1.5c packed brown sugar 1.5c whipping cream 2t cinnamon 1t ginger 1t cloves 1t nutmeg 1t salt  Whipped Cream  250ml whipping cream 1T white sugar 1/2t vanilla extract  Method Blind-bake pie shells  Place foil or parchment into each pie shell and fill with dry beans, pasta or other baking weights Bake at 400°F (200°C) for 10 mins Remove foil and weights Bake for another 5–10 mins until golden brown  Prepare filling  Beat eggs in a medium bowl Add the sugar, pumpkin and cream then whisk to combine Add spices and finish whisking Place pre-baked pie shells on a cookie sheet Divide filling evenly between the shells until 75%–90% full Place on middle rack at 350°F for about 1 hour or until knife inserted near centre comes out clean  Whip cream immediately before serving  Pour cream into small bowl Add sugar and vanilla Whip with electric mixer (or whisk if you need a workout) Dollop over slices of pie  </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analogue Journey Part 4 Fountain Pens</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-4-fountain-pens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-4-fountain-pens/</guid>
      
        <description>This is the third article in my series about exploring a more analogue existence. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested you may want to check out part 1, part 2, and part 3 before continuing.
I always thought that fountain pens were kind of neat. A quaint throwback to a simpler time where people put pen to paper when issuing an invitation to dinner, and when manners and etiquette were the order of the day.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analogue Journey Part 3 Bullet Journal Exploration</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-3-bullet-journal-exploration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-3-bullet-journal-exploration/</guid>
      
        <description>This is the third article in my series about exploring a more analogue existence. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested you may want to check out part 1 and part 2 before continuing.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with a slightly (drastically?) more analogue lifestyle for the past few months. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I&amp;rsquo;m becoming some kind of anti-tech zealot, just that I think I can find a bit more balance in my life. I&amp;rsquo;ve written before about my adoption of notebooks and paper for my handwritten notes at work, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t talk much about the how.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analogue Journey Part 2 Re Educating</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-2-re-educating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-2-re-educating/</guid>
      
        <description>This is the second article in my series about exploring a more analogue existence. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested you may want to check out part 1 before continuing.
The second part of this tale starts a very long time ago. My relationship with notes and note-taking is one fraught with missteps, mistrust and frustration. I had always been a decent student. Mainly, I would later learn, because I had a pretty good memory &amp;ndash; particularly for things that I hear.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analogue Journey Part 1: Digital Catalyst</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-1-digital-catalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-1-digital-catalyst/</guid>
      
        <description>About four months ago I declared bankruptcy &amp;ndash; of a sort. It was a kind of technological bankruptcy. This is the the tale of that decision but to find its roots I need to take you back to a time before I&amp;rsquo;d come to this realization. A time when, for me, technology could solve all of my problems. This goes back years &amp;ndash; though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how many at this point.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediterranean Pasta Salad</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/mediterranean-pasta-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/mediterranean-pasta-salad/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  1 box (454g) fusili 1 cup diced, seeded cucumber 1 cup diced red bell pepper 1 cup crumbled feta  Dressing  1/3 cup balsamic vinegar 1/4 cup olive oil 1 tsp garlic powder 1 tsp oregano 1/2 tsp salt optional: 1 tsp chili flakes  Method  Cook pasta per package directions Shock pasta in cold water to stop cooking, drain thoroughly Combine dressing ingredients in a large bowl Add pasta, pepper, cucumber and feta to bowl and combine Let it sit for at least 30 mins  NOTE: This is an excellent make-ahead recipe, will keep in the fridge for a week.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaghetti Marghertia Casserole</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/spaghetti-marghertia-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/spaghetti-marghertia-casserole/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  2 cans tomatoes (whole, diced or crushed) 2 tbsp olive oil 2 garlic cloves, smashed 1 tbsp dried basil 1 tbsp dried oregano 1 box (375g) spaghetti 6-8 slices mozzarella  Directions  Preheat oven to 425 degrees F (220 degrees C). Bring a pan of salted water to a boil for the pasta, cook for 6-8 mins, should not be completely done. Place oil in pan, and add garlic, sauté for 2-3 mins.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Hyper-V on Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/05/getting-started-with-hyper-v-on-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/05/getting-started-with-hyper-v-on-windows-10/</guid>
      
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently moved to Windows 10 after about a decade swimming in the Apple Kool-aid. While I&amp;rsquo;ve not been away from Windows entirely (I use it at work) I haven&amp;rsquo;t spent any time exploring some of the newer technologies introduced by the Redmond crew in the last few years.
Something that comes as a feature for the Pro and Enterprise versions of Windows 10 is Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s VM Hypervisor technology Hyper-V. If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with it, this is comparable to something like Oracle&amp;rsquo;s VirtualBox.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like a Yoyo</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/05/like-a-yoyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/05/like-a-yoyo/</guid>
      
        <description>I bought a ticket. The steam liner is in dry dock.
Sometimes you have a good idea. An idea that will, in the long run at least, save you time. That idea makes so much sense you can explain it to other people and they shout &amp;ldquo;Yes! I get it! You should totally build a steam liner!&amp;rdquo;
But you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t.
There are ways to get across the ocean. You can buy a boat.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Report Little Brother</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/04/book-report-little-brother/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/04/book-report-little-brother/</guid>
      
        <description>Set in mid-2000s San Francisco, [Cory Doctorow][craphound]&amp;rsquo;s Little Brother brings a tale of what can go wrong when yuo have a society that values compliance over independence.
A story of technology innovation, [hacker culture][wiki-hackerculture], information sharing and data freedom all set against the backdrop of a modern-day terrorism nightmare. Cory Doctorow highlights a number of different things in our everyday world that allow other people to learn more about you, to track you and build a profile about you.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Hardening Strategies</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/03/server-hardening-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/03/server-hardening-strategies/</guid>
      
        <description>Staying secure is a full-time gig. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter whether we&amp;rsquo;re talking a datacentre or your smartphone, there are always steps to be taken to keep your machines and your data as safe as possible. With the increasing popularity of virtualization for applications and services and the ability for people to &amp;ldquo;roll your own&amp;rdquo; cloud comes the need to secure those machines. This becomes increasingly challenging when you consider the fact that by their very nature these machines are constantly exposed to the Internet.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vivaldi Chrome Reimagined</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/03/vivaldi-chrome-reimagined/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/03/vivaldi-chrome-reimagined/</guid>
      
        <description>For several years I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to make the switch to Chrome from Firefox, but the lack of a couple of key plugins has held me back. One of these was the way that windowed plugins were handled initially (the popup for LastPass in Chrome was hideous, but that&amp;rsquo;s no longer an issue.)
The bigger issue for me was the lack of a good vertical tabs plugin for Chrome. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried several tabs but none of them seem to work the way I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten used to with the venerable Tree Style Tabs in Firefox.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think Different(ly)</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/02/think-differently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/02/think-differently/</guid>
      
        <description>In a recent conversation with Knightwise we were musing that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem that it&amp;rsquo;s very long since we were both ragging on Dave to get off Windows and get a Mac. Today we&amp;rsquo;re both seriously entertaining the possibility that our next primary computing device might be running an OS from Redmond. What changed? Has Windows gotten that much better?
Yes. It&amp;rsquo;s undeniably better.
But we&amp;rsquo;re also different.
And Apple is different.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Report Hamlet&#39;s Blackberry</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/02/book-report-hamlets-blackberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/02/book-report-hamlets-blackberry/</guid>
      
        <description>Title: Hamlet&amp;rsquo;s Blackberry Author: William Powers
I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to get this book read for about the last 18 months. It had come highly recommended by a friend who found the book to be a good look into the technological overload of our modern times, and the inherent constant connectivity to the crowds provided by the Internet.
It took me quite a while to get into this book. Powers&#39; continual assertion that the technology that we have come to rely on is disconnecting us from ourselves, and our reality.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>