<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal-development on Keith Murray</title>
    <link>https://kdmurray.com/tags/personal-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal-development on Keith Murray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <copyright>2006-{{ YEAR }} Keith Murray</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kdmurray.com/tags/personal-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Year of Self</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/01/year-of-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/01/year-of-self/</guid>
      
        <description>For the past couple of years I&amp;rsquo;ve eschewed the practice of the New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolution in favour of broader goals or themes for the year. These have been helpful for me in providing an overall direction or guidepost for me as I work to make incremental improvements or changes throughout the year.
Where I&amp;rsquo;ve been&amp;hellip; The first of these, &amp;ldquo;Year of Less&amp;rdquo;, helped me to de-clutter mentally and physically, as well as direct my efforts towards a few specific projects and tasks.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Isn&#39;t Easy</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/simple-isnt-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/simple-isnt-easy/</guid>
      
        <description>Simple and easy &amp;ndash; These are two words that the English language allows people to confuse and that often become the source of misunderstandings of all sorts of sayings, advice, instructions and all manner of other communication.
What&amp;rsquo;s the difference? Easy is a measure of difficulty. If something is easy to do, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t require a great deal of effort and most people will be able to complete the task. The level of ease may depend on other factors, tall people can reach things more easily than short people for example, but generally speaking if something is easy the majority of people will be able to do it without much stress or difficulty.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharpen the Saw or Something</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/07/sharpen-the-saw-or-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/07/sharpen-the-saw-or-something/</guid>
      
        <description>Writing software is something I&amp;rsquo;ve loved to do for a very long time. But a little over a decade ago I made some career choices that meant my day-to-day no longer involved the production of code. I became an amateur developer. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve noodled around with things here and there, and have even managed to write some code that I or a small number of other people have used, but I find it hard to prioritize the time to do these things.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>