<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Keith Murray</title>
    <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Keith Murray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <copyright>2006-{{ YEAR }} Keith Murray</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:56:21 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kdmurray.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Migrated to GHP</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/06/migrated-to-ghp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 12:20:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/06/migrated-to-ghp/</guid>
      
        <description>Migration Complete!</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Analog Tools</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/06/using-analog-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 15:46:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2021/06/using-analog-tools/</guid>
      
        <description>For the last four years I&amp;rsquo;ve been a fountain pen user, some might even say an enthusiast. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using very old technology to help me navigate my otherwise very modern and digital world. Why? Because it makes me think&amp;hellip; and it&amp;rsquo;s fun.
I never grew up with fountain pens. I understand that there are places in the world today that still tech kids to write with them, and that in many cases those students can&amp;rsquo;t wait to get away from these messy devices and start using something more modern like a ballpoint pen.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WSL Manual Install</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/07/wsl-manual-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/07/wsl-manual-install/</guid>
      
        <description>If you happen to be in a situation where you would like to take advantage of Microsoft Windows subsystem for Linux but don&amp;rsquo;t have access to the Microsoft store, there is hope. The one largest caveat is that you need to have permission to install the windows subsystem for, without that the rest of this advice is useless, but once you have done that and rebooted your machine you&amp;rsquo;re ready to move on to the next phase which is find yourself some Linux.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year of Self</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/01/year-of-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2019/01/year-of-self/</guid>
      
        <description>For the past couple of years I&amp;rsquo;ve eschewed the practice of the New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolution in favour of broader goals or themes for the year. These have been helpful for me in providing an overall direction or guidepost for me as I work to make incremental improvements or changes throughout the year.
Where I&amp;rsquo;ve been&amp;hellip; The first of these, &amp;ldquo;Year of Less&amp;rdquo;, helped me to de-clutter mentally and physically, as well as direct my efforts towards a few specific projects and tasks.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Resolutions</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/agile-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/agile-resolutions/</guid>
      
        <description>We&amp;rsquo;re coming up to the end of the year again. I&amp;rsquo;m already starting to see the conversations starting about one of my most hated holiday season traditions: New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolutions.
Why am I such a grinch about self improvement? Why be opposed to people making a change for the better? I&amp;rsquo;m not, and I&amp;rsquo;m not. It&amp;rsquo;s not the change, or even the resolution itself that I have problems with, it&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;New Year&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; bit, and all of the associated issues that come with it.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Isn&#39;t Easy</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/simple-isnt-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/12/simple-isnt-easy/</guid>
      
        <description>Simple and easy &amp;ndash; These are two words that the English language allows people to confuse and that often become the source of misunderstandings of all sorts of sayings, advice, instructions and all manner of other communication.
What&amp;rsquo;s the difference? Easy is a measure of difficulty. If something is easy to do, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t require a great deal of effort and most people will be able to complete the task. The level of ease may depend on other factors, tall people can reach things more easily than short people for example, but generally speaking if something is easy the majority of people will be able to do it without much stress or difficulty.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharpen the Saw or Something</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/07/sharpen-the-saw-or-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2018/07/sharpen-the-saw-or-something/</guid>
      
        <description>Writing software is something I&amp;rsquo;ve loved to do for a very long time. But a little over a decade ago I made some career choices that meant my day-to-day no longer involved the production of code. I became an amateur developer. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve noodled around with things here and there, and have even managed to write some code that I or a small number of other people have used, but I find it hard to prioritize the time to do these things.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>