<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>procrastination on Keith Murray</title>
    <link>https://kdmurray.com/tags/procrastination/</link>
    <description>Recent content in procrastination on Keith Murray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kdmurray.com/tags/procrastination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analogue Journey Part 3 Bullet Journal Exploration</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-3-bullet-journal-exploration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-3-bullet-journal-exploration/</guid>
      
        <description>This is the third article in my series about exploring a more analogue existence. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested you may want to check out part 1 and part 2 before continuing.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with a slightly (drastically?) more analogue lifestyle for the past few months. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I&amp;rsquo;m becoming some kind of anti-tech zealot, just that I think I can find a bit more balance in my life. I&amp;rsquo;ve written before about my adoption of notebooks and paper for my handwritten notes at work, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t talk much about the how.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analogue Journey Part 2 Re Educating</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-2-re-educating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/09/analogue-journey-part-2-re-educating/</guid>
      
        <description>This is the second article in my series about exploring a more analogue existence. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested you may want to check out part 1 before continuing.
The second part of this tale starts a very long time ago. My relationship with notes and note-taking is one fraught with missteps, mistrust and frustration. I had always been a decent student. Mainly, I would later learn, because I had a pretty good memory &amp;ndash; particularly for things that I hear.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like a Yoyo</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/05/like-a-yoyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/blog/2017/05/like-a-yoyo/</guid>
      
        <description>I bought a ticket. The steam liner is in dry dock.
Sometimes you have a good idea. An idea that will, in the long run at least, save you time. That idea makes so much sense you can explain it to other people and they shout &amp;ldquo;Yes! I get it! You should totally build a steam liner!&amp;rdquo;
But you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t.
There are ways to get across the ocean. You can buy a boat.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>