<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cookbooks on K.D. Murray</title>
    <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cookbooks on K.D. Murray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 15:18:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thai Red Curry With Prawns</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/thai-red-curry-with-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 15:18:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/thai-red-curry-with-prawns/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  200-250 grams frozen raw prawns 1 small onion 2 carrots 1 broccoli crown 1 bell pepper 2 cloves garlic 1 tbsp fresh grated ginger 2 tbsp red curry paste 1 can coconut milk (full-fat) 1 tbsp brown sugar (or demerera, or coconut sugar) 1 tbsp soy sauce optional 1-2 jalepeño or other chiles to taste  Method  Thaw prawns in cool water while you prep the vegetables Break down all the veggies into pieces that will cook in a similar amount of time  peppers will cook the quickest looking for ~2 cups of veggies   Heat coconut milk and curry paste over medium heat, stirring occasionally until paste is fully incorporated and bubbles begin to appear Add soy sauce, sugar, garlic, ginger and onions to the coconut milk, simmer for 2 minutes Add prawns and simmer for 5 minutes - add 2 minutes if not thawed Add veggies in stages by hardness every 3-4 minutes Once all ingredients are added, cook until desired doneness of veggies is reached, probably 3-4 minutes This recipe goes really well with Baked Brown Rice  </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Brown Rice</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/baked-brown-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/baked-brown-rice/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  1 cups long grain brown rice 2 cups water 1 tbsp butter or olive oil 1/2 tsp salt  Method  Preheat oven to 400°F (200°C) Boil watter Combine all ingredients in a covered casserole Cover and bake for 1 hour  If your oven heats unevenly you may need to rotate the casserole</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Zucchini Muffins</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/banana-zucchini-muffins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 17:54:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/banana-zucchini-muffins/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  2 1/2 cups all purpose flour 1 1/2 tsp baking soda 1 1/2 tsp baking powder 1 tsp salt 4 bananas, mashed 1 cup zucchini, grated 1/3 cup brown sugar 1 egg, beaten 1/2 cup butter, melted * 1 tsp vanilla optional 1/3 cup shredded unsweetened coconut optional 1/3 cup chopped walnuts  Method  Pre-heat oven to 350 degrees F (180 degrees C) Combine sugar, bananas, zucchini, butter, egg and vanilla in a mixing bowl Mix remaining ingredients in a large bowl Pour wet over dry and mix just until combined DO NOT OVERMIX YOUR MUFFINS Portion into muffin tins and bake for 20-25 minutes  For mini-muffin tins, bake 15-20 mins    </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown Sugar Spice Rub</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/brown-sugar-spice-rub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/brown-sugar-spice-rub/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  4 parts brown sugar 2 parts kosher salt 1 part chili powder 1 part spices  cumin paprika garlic powder onion powder black pepper    Method  Mix all ingredients in a jar Add a lid and keep tightly sealed between uses Sprinkle liberally on chicken, pork or whatever else needs to be kicked up a notch  Note: Rub can also be made without sugar for applications where other sources of sweetness exist: i.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split Pea Soup</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/split-pea-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/split-pea-soup/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  2 Tbsp unsalted butter 1 cup chopped onion 1 Tbsp minced garlic 1 pinch kosher salt 12 oz (350g) green or yellow split peas 5 cups chicken broth 1Tbsp curry powder 1/2 cup diced ham (optional)  Method  Sweat the onions in the butter and salt for 2–3 mins until translucent Add the garlic to the sweat for 1–2 mins Add curry powder, peas and chicken broth Bring to a boil Cover and reduce to a simmer Simmer until peas are tender and not holding their shape (approx 40 minutes) Adjust seasoning to taste Puree with a stick blender (carefully, it&amp;rsquo;s hot!</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clasic Pumpkin Pie</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/clasic-pumpkin-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/clasic-pumpkin-pie/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients Crust  2 9&amp;quot; frozen pie shells Yes, making your own would be more &amp;ldquo;classic.&amp;rdquo; I never do.  Filling  4 eggs 28oz pumpkin puree 1.5c packed brown sugar 1.5c whipping cream 2t cinnamon 1t ginger 1t cloves 1t nutmeg 1t salt  Whipped Cream  250ml whipping cream 1T white sugar 1/2t vanilla extract  Method Blind-bake pie shells  Place foil or parchment into each pie shell and fill with dry beans, pasta or other baking weights Bake at 400°F (200°C) for 10 mins Remove foil and weights Bake for another 5–10 mins until golden brown  Prepare filling  Beat eggs in a medium bowl Add the sugar, pumpkin and cream then whisk to combine Add spices and finish whisking Place pre-baked pie shells on a cookie sheet Divide filling evenly between the shells until 75%–90% full Place on middle rack at 350°F for about 1 hour or until knife inserted near centre comes out clean  Whip cream immediately before serving  Pour cream into small bowl Add sugar and vanilla Whip with electric mixer (or whisk if you need a workout) Dollop over slices of pie  </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediterranean Pasta Salad</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/mediterranean-pasta-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/mediterranean-pasta-salad/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  1 box (454g) fusili 1 cup diced, seeded cucumber 1 cup diced red bell pepper 1 cup crumbled feta  Dressing  1/3 cup balsamic vinegar 1/4 cup olive oil 1 tsp garlic powder 1 tsp oregano 1/2 tsp salt optional: 1 tsp chili flakes  Method  Cook pasta per package directions Shock pasta in cold water to stop cooking, drain thoroughly Combine dressing ingredients in a large bowl Add pasta, pepper, cucumber and feta to bowl and combine Let it sit for at least 30 mins  NOTE: This is an excellent make-ahead recipe, will keep in the fridge for a week.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaghetti Marghertia Casserole</title>
      <link>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/spaghetti-marghertia-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdmurray.com/cookbook/spaghetti-marghertia-casserole/</guid>
      
        <description>Ingredients  2 cans tomatoes (whole, diced or crushed) 2 tbsp olive oil 2 garlic cloves, smashed 1 tbsp dried basil 1 tbsp dried oregano 1 box (375g) spaghetti 6-8 slices mozzarella  Directions  Preheat oven to 425 degrees F (220 degrees C). Bring a pan of salted water to a boil for the pasta, cook for 6-8 mins, should not be completely done. Place oil in pan, and add garlic, sauté for 2-3 mins.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>